taxipark.com.ng 2013-05-26

# We got you covered - TaxiPark Nigeria

####  __Terms & Conditions

**Terms of website use**  
This page (together with the documents referred to herein) sets out the terms of use on which you may use the website www.taxipark.com.ng ("the Site"), whether as a guest (i.e. non-registered user) or a registered user. Please read these terms of use carefully before you start to use the Site. By using the Site, you indicate that you accept these terms of use and that you agree to abide by them. If you do not agree to these terms of use, please refrain from using the Site. If you are a minor (i.e. you are younger than 18 years of age) you hereby declare that you have obtained the authorisation of your parent or guardian to agree to these Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy. 

**Information about TaxiPark.**  
The TaxiPark revolution began in February 2012. Our mission was simple - To give passengers and drivers alike a more reliable, user-friendly and safe way to move around the city. We all know how unorganized, inconvenient and not easily accessible getting a taxi in Lagos is, that's why we built our service to be as convenient as possible. We are proud to say we have the 1st online taxi booking service in Nigeria and 50+ licensed cabs registered on our platform. We also understand how hard it is for taxi/car hiring companies to manage drivers and track cars. So we developed our TaxiPark Cloud Console, giving taxi companies the power to track and mange driver movements. 

**How it works - Passengers**  
TaxiPark allows you to book a taxi ride, wherever you are, directly from your computer or mobile phone (well, in Lagos for now, of course). No more phone calls. No more flagging down taxis on the highway or looking for the closest taxi park to you.   
Need to book in advance? No problem. Simply schedule a time and a taxi will be right there. It's that easy   
**How it works - Taxi/Car Hiring Companies**  
TaxiPark will bring you more high value account and cash jobs. Manage and track all bookings in real time using the TaxiPark Cloud Console via a PC. 

**Accessing our site**  
Access to the Site is permitted on a limited basis and for personal use only. TaxiPark reserves the right to withdraw or amend the service it provides on the site without notice. TaxiPark will not be liable if for any reason the Site is unavailable at any time or for any period. The Site is available on a number of different devices and these terms of use shall apply on any device, both current and future. By using the Site, you hereby acknowledge that TaxiPark will not be liable under any circumstances for damage caused to your device or software. 

**Use of the Site does not entitle you to:**  
Download (other than page caching) or modify the Site, or any part of it, except with the express written consent of TaxiPark;  
Use the Site or any part of it for any resale or commercial use of the services on offer or its contents, except with the express written consent of TaxiPark.  
Any collection and use of any product listings, descriptions or prices.  
Any use of data mining robots or other data gathering/extraction tools.  
Attempt or assist anyone to attempt to reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, adapt.  
Modify, copy, reproduce, sub-license, make available to the public, create any derivative works.  
From, distribute, commercially exploit, transmit or otherwise use the Site, or any part of it, in any way.  
From time to time, TaxiPark may restrict access to some parts of the Site, or the entire Site, to users who have registered with TaxiPark. 

If you choose, or you are provided with, a user identification code, password or any other piece of information as part of the security procedures, you must treat such information as confidential, and you must not disclose it to any third party. You are responsible for restricting access to your computer where appropriate. You hereby agree to be responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and accept responsibility for all activities that take place via your account or password. TaxiPark reserves the right to disable any user identification code or password, whether chosen by you or allocated by TaxiPark, at any time, if in its opinion you have failed to comply with any of the provisions of these terms of use. 

You are responsible for making all necessary arrangements in order to access the Site. You are also responsible for ensuring that all persons who access the Site through your internet connection are aware of these terms, and that they comply with them. 

**Intellectual property rights**  
TaxiPark is the owner or the licensee of all (registered and unregistered) intellectual property rights in the Site, and in the material published on it other than any third party intellectual property rights. Those works are protected by copyright laws, trademark laws and treaties around the world. All such rights are reserved. 

The trademarks, logos, and service marks (collectively the "Trademarks") displayed on this site are TaxiPark's registered and unregistered Trademarks other than any third party intellectual property rights. TaxiPark's Trademarks may not be used in connection with any product or service that is not its own, in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among customers, or in any manner that disparages or discredits TaxiPark. 

In addition, text, graphics, logos, icons, images, audio clips, video clips, digital downloads, data compilations, interactive content and scripts are TaxiPark's intellectual property and may not be copied, used or imitated without the prior written consent of TaxiPark. The compilation and appearance of all content on the Site is the exclusive property of TaxiPark. Nothing contained on the Site should be construed as granting, by implication, or otherwise, any license or right to use any of TaxiPark's intellectual property rights or those of any third party without TaxiPark's express written permission. 

One or more patents owned by TaxiPark apply to its Site and to the features and services accessible via the Site. Your misuse of the intellectual property displayed on the Site, or any other content on the Site is strictly prohibited. 

You may print off copies, and may download extracts, of any page(s) from the Site for your personal reference and you may draw the attention of others within your organisation to material posted on the Site. 

You must not modify the paper or digital copies of any materials you have printed off or downloaded in any way, and you must not use any illustrations, photographs, video or audio sequences or any graphics separately from any accompanying text. 

You may not otherwise reproduce, modify copy or distribute or use for commercial purposes any of the materials or contents of the site without TaxiPark's permission. TaxiPark's status (and that of any identified contributors) as the authors of material on the Site and the owners of the intellectual property on the Site must always be acknowledged. If you print off, copy or download any part of the Site in breach of these terms of use, your right to use the Site will cease immediately and you must, at TaxiPark's request, return or destroy any copies of the materials you have made. You are also advised that we will enforce TaxiPark's intellectual property rights to the fullest extent permitted by law. If TaxiPark decides not to enforce or exercise its legal rights in respect of a breach of its intellectual property rights at any given time, this does not prevent TaxiPark from later exercising or enforcing such rights. 

**Disclosure of data to taxi driver**  
You hereby provide TaxiPark with full, irrevocable authority to provide data concerning your name, mobile telephone number, and journey, and pick-up time to TaxiPark's pool of taxi drivers in your location. This data will be used to select your taxi driver from TaxiPark's pool and will enable the taxi driver to pick you up at the chosen location and take you to your destination. No other data about you will be disclosed to the pool of taxi drivers or your specific taxi driver. 

**Non Agency**  
The Site provides you with access to a large number of independent taxi drivers and Taxi Companies in your locality. Your contract for the hire of a taxi is direct with your taxi driver (Verified Lagos taxis) or taxi Companies. TaxiPark is not a party to that contract. TaxiPark therefore accepts no liability whatsoever for any loss(es) that you suffer as a result of your contract with your taxi driver. In no event shall TaxiPark, its officers, directors or employees be liable to you for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, punitive or consequential damages resulting from any financial or personal injury or property damage, resulting from your use of a taxi driver contacted through the Site. Notwithstanding the above, in the event that a court or other authority finds that TaxiPark is liable, in whole or in part, you will hereby indemnify TaxiPark against any loss(es) suffered by yourself as a result of the respective taxi journey. 

**The Site changes regularly**  
TaxiPark aims to update the Site regularly, and may change the content at any time. If the need arises, TaxiPark may suspend access to the Site, or close it indefinitely. Any of the material on the Site may be out of date at any given time, and TaxiPark is under no obligation to update such material. 

####  __Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
TaxiPark is duly registered in Nigeria with its office at 6B Bendel Close Victoria Island. Lagos. We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Safeguarding your personal information is important to us and we recognize the responsibility you entrust us with when providing your personal data. This Privacy Policy details how your personal information is used by TaxiPark both actively and passively, when you use the website, www.takipark.com.ng ("the Site"), and/or the TaxiPark Mobile Telephone Application ("the App"). Whatever information we may collect from you via the Site and/or the App, we wish to state how we will use it, whether we will disclose information provided by you to third parties and the use of "cookies" on the Site and by the App. By using TaxiPark's services or registering, downloading information or entering the Site and/or the App you consent to the processing (collecting, using, disclosing, retaining or disposing of personal data) of your information under the terms of this policy. The information TaxiPark holds about you can be held on computer and/or paper files. 

**Information TaxiPark may collect from you**  
TaxiPark may collect data about you relating to: The provision of services, or online content in order to deal with your requests and enquiries. This includes data provided at the time of subscribing to any services TaxiPark offers, downloading data posted on the Site and/or the App, posting material or requesting further services; data in connection with or participation in any promotions or competitions sponsored, promoted or offered by us and/or any third party and any data provided to us by way of feedback, profile forms or site issues; you contacting us, for example by email, post or telephone, in which case TaxiPark may keep a record of that correspondence to respond to your enquiries and improve its services. Thereafter, TaxiPark may use your email address to contact you about its services; Other information from your interaction with the Site and/or the App, services, content and advertising, including computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the Site, Ad data, IP address, standard web log information and the resources that you access, whether this is required for TaxiPark's own purposes or otherwise. 

**IP addresses and cookies**  
TaxiPark may collect information about your computer and/or your mobile telephone device, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to TaxiPark's advertisers. This is statistical data about TaxiPark's users browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. For the same reason, TaxiPark may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer and/or your mobile telephone device. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's and/or mobile telephone device's hard drive. They help us to improve the Site and to deliver a better and more personalized service. They enable us: 

To estimate TaxiPark's audience size and usage pattern;  
To store information about your preferences and so allow us to customize the Site according to your individual interests;  
To continually improve TaxiPark's services;  
To recognize you when you return to the Site.  
You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, TaxiPark's system will issue cookies when you log on to the Site and/or use the App. You may wish to look at http://www.aboutcookies.org/ which has further information on cookies and how to manage them. 

**Where will TaxiPark store your personal data?**  
The data that TaxiPark collects from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a remote Location in the US or in Nigeria. Where TaxiPark has given you (or where you have chosen) a username, login or password which enables you to access certain parts of the Site and/or the App, you are responsible for keeping this information confidential. TaxiPark asks you not to share a username, login or password with anyone. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet and/or by mobile telephone applications is not completely secure. Although TaxiPark will do its best to protect your personal data, TaxiPark cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Site and/or the App; any transmission is at your own risk. Once TaxiPark has received your information, it will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. 

TaxiPark restricts access to your data to individuals who need access to it in order to process it on TaxiPark's behalf. These individuals, were employees, are bound by confidentiality agreements and will be subject to disciplinary proceedings should TaxiPark find that it has failed to meet standards in looking after your data. TaxiPark cannot accept any liability for employees or agents acting outside its normal course of business. 

**Uses made of the information**  
TaxiPark uses information held about you in the following ways:  
To ensure that content on the Site and/or the App is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer and/or your mobile telephone;

To provide you with information, products or services that you request from TaxiPark or which may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes;  
To carry out TaxiPark's obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and TaxiPark (including but not limited to pick-up and drop-off destinations);  
To allow you to participate in interactive features of TaxiPark's service, when you choose to do so;  
To contact you for your views on TaxiPark's services and to notify you about changes or developments to TaxiPark's service;  
To improve the Site and/or the App including tailoring it to your needs;  
To use GPS to identify the location of users.  
TaxiPark may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and TaxiPark or they may contact you about these by email, post or telephone.

**Disclosure of your information**  
TaxiPark may disclose your personal information to any member of TaxiPark's group, which means TaxiPark's ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries. TaxiPark may also use your information to send you offers and news about TaxiPark's services or those of other carefully selected companies which TaxiPark thinks may be of interest to you. TaxiPark may contact you by post, email, telephone or fax for these purposes.  
TaxiPark may also pass your information on to any successor or potential successor in title to the business and suppliers that process data on TaxiPark's behalf both in the Nigeria and abroad. TaxiPark may also use and disclose information in aggregate (so that no individual customers are identified) for marketing and strategic purposes. 

**Your rights**  
You have the right to request that TaxiPark does not process your personal data for marketing purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by emailing legal@taxipark.com.ng  
You also have the right to ask TaxiPark to amend any data it holds about you if it is inaccurate or misleading as to any matter of fact and a right to ask for a copy of the data that TaxiPark holds relating to you. TaxiPark also asks that you provide it with two forms of photographic identification so that TaxiPark can verify your identity. Any request to amend TaxiPark's records should be in writing and addressed to it by post at 6B Bendel Close off Aboyade Cole Street, Victoria Island, Lagos or by email at legal@taxiPark.com.ng 

From time to time TaxiPark may post links to third party websites on the Site and/or the App. These links are provided as a courtesy to TaxiPark's customers and are not administered or verified in any way by TaxiPark. Such links are accessed by you at your own risk and TaxiPark makes no representations or warranties about the content of such websites and cannot be held liable for any losses you suffer as a result of using such third party websites. TaxiPark may provide links to third party websites that use cookies. As a result, TaxiPark strongly recommends that you read the privacy policies of any third party websites before you provide any information to them. 

**Changes to TaxiPark's privacy policy**  
Any changes TaxiPark may make to its Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page. This Privacy Policy will be updated from time to time, so you may want to check it each time you send TaxiPark personal information. The date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page. 

**Contact**  
Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to legal@taxipark.com.ng 

**Date of most recent update: 19/02/2013**
